I'll go cook.
Let me help you.
Do you need me to do anything?
Okay.
This looks really good.
Have a taste.
Did I cook for you often before?
What?
You've been reborn many times, right?
When we were together before,
did I cook for you often?
Aren't you going to have a bite before you go?
No, I have a flight to catch.
When I'm not home,
look for Pei Ning if you need anything.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
Let me try it first.
It's really good.
I didn't expect you to be such a good cook.
I feel like you could open a private restaurant.
Is it really that good?
I'm serious, it's really delicious.
Then try this.
Shiya.
I missed out on how good you are before.
But this time,
I won't let you go no matter what.
Do you want some wine?
I'll go get it.
Okay.
Why did you only bring one glass?
I'm sorry,
Pei Song.
Forgive me, but I can't say yes to you.
There are some things
I must face on my own.
Time to take your medicine.
Just leave.
I don't want to see you.
The Pei family doesn't have a descendant like you.
Shiya and I truly love each other.
You're lying.
Don't think just because I'm old
that I don't know anything.
That thing you're making,
the big data AI...
It's impossible to succeed.
Enough!
What do you know?
It's you who
never looked at me properly since I was a kid!
I do exactly what my brother does.
Why does he get everything?
How am I inferior to him?
Your brother does those things
because of his passion.
But you?
You just do it out of jealousy.
Your intentions are impure,
so naturally, you fail.
Nonsense!
You're just biased!
You'll never surpass your brother.
Say that again.
And I'll never admit you're better than him.
The Pei family
only has one grandson, your brother.
You don't deserve the name Pei.
Say that again!
My name is Pei!
Is my name Pei or not?
My name is Pei.
My name is Pei Ning!
Stop!
Why are you here?
Do you want to beat your brother?
I'll marry you.
I'll sign a divorce agreement.
Then you record a video of me and send it to Pei Song.
I'll make it clear to him
to stop bothering me.
Really?
Really.
Okay.
Brother,
just sign this divorce agreement.
Shiya doesn't love you at all.
This time,
I won.
Pei Song, let's get a divorce.
Our marriage was just a contract anyway.
Don't come looking for me.
With Pei Ning,
I'll be very happy.
Pei Song, let's get a divorce.
Our marriage was an agreement in the first place.
Don't come looking for me.
Being with Pei Ning,
I will be very happy.
Don't you think
the encryption method of this code
is very similar to Morse code?
The key is the codebook.
An encryption method
can often
reveal a person's character.
If you are in danger in the future,
you can use your favorite book as a codebook.
Shiya.